Finding Aid for School of Education (University of Michigan) Records, 1904-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Minutes
  - Executive Committee [Paper], 1999-2005
    - May 2000 (Box 53)
    - June 2000 (Box 53)
    - September 2000 (Box 53)
    - October-December 2000 (Box 53)
    - January-February 2001 (Box 53)
    - March-April 2001 (Box 53)
    - May 2001 (Box 53)
    - June 2001 (Box 53)
    - September 11, 2001 (Box 53)
    - September 2001 (Box 53)
    - October-November 2001 (Box 53)
    - December 2001 (Box 53)
    - January-February 2002 (Box 53)
    - March 2002 (Box 53)
    - April 2002 (Box 54)
    - May 2002 (Box 54)
    - June 2002 (Box 54)
    - September-December 2002 (Box 54)
    - January-March 2003 (Box 54)
    - April 1, 2003 (Box 54)
    - April 15, 2003 (Box 54)
    - April 29, 2003 (Box 54)
    - May 2003 (Box 54)
    - June 2003 (Box 54)
    - September-December 2003 (Box 54)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 54)
    - January-March 2004 (Box 54)
    - March 16, 2004 (Box 54)
    - March 30, 2004 (Box 54)
    - April-May 2004 (Box 54)
    - June 2004 (Box 54)
    - September-December 2004 (Box 54)
    - January-February 2005 (Box 54)
    - March 2005 (Box 54)
    - April 5, 2005, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - April 19, 2005 (Box 54)
    - May-June 2005 (Box 54)
  - Executive Committee [Electronic], 2004-2010
    - 2004-2005
    - 2005-2006
    - 2006-2007
    - 2007-2008
    - 2009-2010
- Dean's Files
  The Dean's Files series constitutes the central file of the dean's office. The first three subseries --1925-1979, covering the tenures of the first five deans; Joan S. Stark, 1978-1983; Carl F. Berger, 1983-1988--are arranged alphabetically. There is some overlap in the subseries as records created under earlier dean's were sometimes not transferred until much later.
  The 2012 accession added symposium and conference materials to the Deans Files 1920-1979 series, located in Boxes 6-12, and extends the Carl F. Berger series, found in Boxes 32-41. The new additions to these series are found in Box 49. The 2012 accession also updated the Deans Files series to include the records of Deans Cecil Miskel, Karen Wixson, and Deborah Ball.
  - 1920-1979, 5 linear feet
    The Dean's Files, 1920-1979 subseries (5 linear feet) cover primarily the tenure of the first five dean's of the School of Education. It represents a large grouping of material kept in the dean's office and arranged alphabetically by topic. The records contain information concerning the history of the School of Education through budget information, Building Committee, and Fresh Air Camp files. The history is also visible in the information on the various units of the School, in particular the Bureau of School Services, Graduate Division, Physical Education, and the Program and Center for Higher Education. The "Flint Public School Survey" taken in 1921-1922 by the faculty, under the supervision of Allen Whitney, gives good insight into the philosophy of the School for that period. There is also information on various educational associations of which the School of Education was a member.
    - Accreditation, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
      (See Also-National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE))
    - Admissions
      - 1970-1978 (Box 6)
      - 1979 (Box 6)
    - Adult and Continuing Education, Program in, 1974-1979 (Box 6)
    - Affirmative Action, 1972-1979 (Box 6)
      (See Also-Program for Educational Opportunity (PEO))
    - Alumni Activities (SOE), 1978-1979 (Box 6)
    - Ann Arbor Public Schools
      - General, 1928-1968 (Box 6)
      - Administration of, 1972 (Box 6)
      - University of Michigan Joint Steering Committee
        - 1969-1970 (Box 6)
        - 1971 (Box 6)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 6)
      - University of Michigan Liaison Committee
        - 1967/68 (Box 6)
        - 1968/69 (Box 6)
        - 1969/70 (Box 6)
      - University of Michigan Steering Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 6)
      - Work Session Meeting, August 27, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Ann Arbor Teaching Center, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Anniversary Celebration, 1939 (Box 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1950-1959 (Box 6)
    - Appraisal Committee, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Black Action Movement (BAM) Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Budget
      - 1970/71 (Box 6)
      - 1971/72 (Box 6)
      - 1973/74 (Box 6)
      - 1974/75 (Box 6)
      - (Budget Conference), 1978 (Box 6)
      - 1978/79
        - General (Box 6)
        - Physical Education, Department of (Box 6)
      - 1979
        - Budget Conference (Box 6)
        - Faculty Merit Evaluation (Box 6)
    - Building Committee
      - General, 1954-1962; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - General, 1963-1968 (Box 7)
      - Cost estimates, 1955-1961 (Box 7)
      - Faculty survey, circa 1955 (Box 7)
      - Library requirements, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
      - Meeting minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 7)
      - Project statement/goals, 1955 (Box 7)
      - Renovation
        - General, 1964-1970 (Box 7)
        - Minutes, 1961-1967 (Box 7)
        - Report, 1970 (Box 7)
      - Site/space, ca, 1956 (Box 7)
    - Bureau of School Services
      - 1970-1976 (Box 7)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 7)
    - By-Laws Committee, 1960-1969 (Box 7)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
      - 1973-1977 (Box 7)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 7)
    - Certification
      (See Also-Teacher Education and Certification)
      - 1904-1926 (Box 7)
      - 1926-1960 (Box 7)
      - 1961-1978 (Box 7)
      - 1979 (Box 7)
    - Council, School of Education (minutes), 1920-1924 (Box 7)
    - Curriculum Coordinating Committee
      - General, 1971-1978 (Box 7)
      - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1945-1952 (Box 7)
    - Deans and Directors Group (Michigan Schools)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 7)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 7)
      - 1971-1979 (Box 7)
    - Deans Council of Eight (State of Michigan) (Box 8)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 8)
      - 1975 (Box 8)
      - 1976 (Box 8)
      - 1977 (Box 8)
      - 1978 (Box 8)
    - Deans Network, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - Deanship of School of Education (SOE)
      - Report on, 1923 (Box 8)
      - Search Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
    - Dearborn Campus
      - General, 1962-1974 (Box 8)
      - Division of Education (executive committee minutes)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 8)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 8)
      - Joint Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 8)
      - Task Force, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
    - Directed Teaching Program
      - 1951-1967 (Box 8)
      - 1968-1973 (Box 8)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - Early Childhood Development and Education, Center for, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
    - Educational Administration, Program in
      - General, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
      - Search Committee for New Staff, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
    - Educational Media Center, 1970-1977; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Educational Psychology, Combined Program, 1966-1978 (Box 8)
    - Educational Reference and Research, Bureau of, 1924-1949 (Box 8)
    - Enrollment
      - 1957-1979 (Box 8)
    - Evaluation Research, Training, and Service, Consortium for (CERTS)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 8)
      - 1979 (Box 8)
    - Extension Service
      - 1967-1977 (Box 8)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - External Review Committee (Eurich report), 1968/69 (Box 8)
    - Faculty
      - Report on Committee and Professional Activities, 1948 (Box 8)
      - Retreat, 1979 (Box 8)
      - Workload, 1961; 1972 (Box 9)
    - Fifty-Year Report (Office of Institutional Research), 1972 (Box 9)
    - Financial Aid
      - 1963-1978 (Box 9)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 9)
    - Flint Campus, 1977-1979 (Box 9)
    - Flint Public School Survey, 1921-1922 (Box 9)
    - Fresh Air Camp
      - 1952-1960 (Box 9)
      - 1966-1971 (Box 9)
      - 1972-1976 (Box 9)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 9)
    - Gerontology, Institute of
      - 1974 (Box 9)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 9)
    - Graduate Committee
      - General, 1975-1979; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Elections, 1975 (Box 9)
      - Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
    - Graduate Enrollment, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
    - Graduate School (Box 9)
      (SEE-Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies)
    - Graduate Study in Teachers' Colleges, 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - Grievance Procedures, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Guidance Counseling, Program in (J program)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 9)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Higher Education, Program and Center
      - 1965-1973 (Box 9)
      - 1974-1977 (Box 9)
      - 1978 (Box 9)
      - 1979 (Box 9)
    - Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies
      - 1978 (Box 9)
      - 1979 (Box 9)
    - ISMRRD (Box 9)
      (SEE-Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of)
    - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1970-1979 (Box 9)
    - Instructional Services, Office of, 1974-1979 (Box 9)
    - Instructional Strategies Services, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Junior Class Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 9)
    - Language Resource Unit (LRU), 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Library (University), 1967-1979 (Box 10)
    - Media Center
      - 1978 (Box 10)
      - 1979 (Box 10)
    - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of
      - 1978 (Box 10)
      - 1979 (Box 10)
    - Michigan Association of Colleges of Teacher Education, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Michigan Department of Education, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Minorities
      - 1968-1970 (Box 10)
      - 1971-1979 (Box 10)
    - Minority Student Affairs, Office of, 1971-1979 (Box 10)
    - Mobilization for Peace, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Moehlman, Arthur B., (professor, School Administrations and Supervision), 1929-1947 (Box 10)
    - Moore, Henry T., President, Skidmore College, 1925-1928 (Box 10)
      (See Also-University Elementary School Building File)
    - Multicultural Education, 1976-1979 (Box 10)
    - Myers, George E. (professor, Vocational Education), 1933-1955 (Box 10)
      (See Also-Vocational Education Department, Report of)
    - National Advisory Committee on Education Reports, 1931 (Box 10)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE)
      (See Also-Accreditation)
      - 1960-1963 (Box 10)
      - 1964-1978 (Box 10)
      - 1979 (Box 10)
    - Occupational Education Program
      - General
        - 1971-1977 (Box 10)
        - 1978 (Box 10)
        - 1979 (Box 10)
      - Minutes, 1971-1975 (Box 10)
    - Petition Expressing Appreciation for SOE Establishment, 1922 (Box 10)
    - Physical Education
      - General
        - 1915-1932 (Box 10)
        - 1966-1977 (Box 10)
        - 1978 (Box 10)
        - 1979 (Box 10)
      - Phase I, 1977 (Box 10)
      - Review Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Professional Organizations, 1935-1950 (Box 10)
    - Professional Training of Teachers, Memo to Regent, 1915 (Box 10)
    - Program for Educational Opportunity, for (PEO)
      (See Also-Affirmative Action)
      - 1970-1976 (Box 10)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 10)
    - Promotions
      - General
        - 1968-1970 (Box 10)
        - 1972 (Box 10)
        - 1973 (Box 10)
        - 1974 (Box 10)
        - 1975 (Box 10)
        - 1976 (Box 10)
        - 1977 (Box 10)
    - Propaganda Analysis, 1939 (Box 10)
    - Public Health Nursing, 1941-1943 (Box 10)
    - Reading, Learning Skills Center, 1969-1979 (Box 10)
    - Reading Program, 1970-1979 (Box 10)
    - Reorganization
      - 1956 (Box 10)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - Research Activities, 1979 (Box 10)
    - School Boards, 1929-1951 (Box 11)
    - Social Foundations Program, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
    - Southeastern Michigan Round Table, 1946-1950 (Box 11)
    - School Boards, 1929-1951 (Box 11)
    - Social Foundations Program, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
    - Southeastern Michigan Round Table, 1946-1950 (Box 11)
    - Special Education
      - 1977-1978 (Box 11)
      - 1979 (Box 11)
    - Speech and Hearing Sciences
      - General
        - 1978 (Box 11)
        - 1979, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Accreditation, 1979 (Box 11)
      - Audit and Budget, 1978 (Box 11)
      - Sussman Report, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
      - Transition, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Staffing Priorities, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
    - Standing Committee Memberships, 1974-1978 (Box 11)
    - State Prison, 1931-1936 (Box 11)
    - State Teachers Colleges of Michigan
      - Cooperation, 1939-1946 (Box 11)
      - Graduate Division Annual Reports
        - 1939/40 (Box 11)
        - 1940/41 (Box 11)
        - 1941/42 (Box 11)
        - 1942/43 (Box 11)
        - 1943/44 (Box 11)
        - 1944/45 (Box 11)
    - Statistics
      - 1957-1964 (Box 11)
      - 1965-1968 (Box 11)
    - Student-Faculty Retreat, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Students for Educational Innovation (SEI)
      - 1968 (Box 11)
      - 1969-1973 (Box 11)
      - 1974-1979 (Box 11)
    - Summer Session, 1913-1954 (Box 11)
    - Taxation, 1932-1934 (Box 11)
    - Teacher Education, Division of
      - General, 1970-1979 (Box 11)
      - Executive Committee (minutes), 1978-1979 (Box 11)
    - Teacher Education and Certification
      (See Also-Certification)
      - Report to the Joint Committee, April 22, 1969 (Box 11)
      - University Committee
        - 1930-1958 (Box 11)
        - 1959-1965 (Box 11)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 11)
        - 1968-1973 (Box 11)
    - Teacher Rating and Merit System, circa 1947 (Box 11)
    - Teaching-Male Instructors, 1929-1946 (Box 11)
    - Tenure Questionnaire, December 1979 (Box 12)
    - Tutorial Project, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
    - Undergraduate Committee meeting minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 12)
    - Undergraduate Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 12)
    - University Elementary School Building File, 1928; 2 folders (Box 12)
      (See Also-Moore, Henry T.)
    - University High School, 1935-1954 (Box 12)
    - University High School Closing
      - General, 1969 (Box 12)
      - Budget Materials, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
      - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Vocational Education Department, Report of, 1948 (Box 12)
      (See Also-Myers, George E.)
    - Western State Teachers College (Kalamazoo), 1940-1941 (Box 12)
    - Wright, L.L. (Superintendent of Ironwood Schools) (paper "The School and the Community"), undated (Box 12)
  - Stark, Joan S., 1930-1988; 1978-1983
    The files of Joan S. Stark (11.5 linear feet) span the years 1930-1983, however the bulk of the materials cover her tenure, 1978-1983. Of particular interest are the Undergraduate Committee Minutes, which include information on policies, courses, and goals of the teacher education program. The researcher will also find substantial information on the various programs within the school, in addition to information gathered for the reorganization. Speeches given by Dean Stark as well as some documentation pertaining to the review of the School which were received in 1998 are located in Box 47.
    - Academic Program Review, 1980-1983 (Box 19)
    - Academic Services
      - 1978 (Box 19)
      - 1979 (Box 19)
      - 1980 (Box 19)
      - 1981 (Box 19)
      - 1982 (Box 19)
    - Accreditation, 1969-1983 (Box 19)
    - Adjunct Instructional Staff, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
    - Admissions, 1980-1983; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Adult and Continuing Education
      - General, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
      - External Degree Program, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
    - Affirmative Action, 1979-1983 (Box 19)
    - Afro-American Studies, Center for, 1969-1976 (Box 19)
    - Allied Health Education, 1979-1982 (Box 19)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teachers Education (annual report), 1948-1973 (Box 19)
    - Anniversary of School of Education (50th), 1971 (Box 19)
    - Ann Arbor Public Schools
      - General, 1968-1980 (Box 19)
      - Collaboration (re: new high school), 1961-1968 (Box 19)
      - Joint Steering Committee
        - General, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
        - Minutes and Members, 1975-1982 (Box 19)
      - Visiting Lecture Agreement, 1980-1983 (Box 19)
    - Annual Awards, 1969-1983 (Box 19)
    - Arabic Language Bilingual Materials Development Center, 1980-1983 (Box 19)
    - "B" Program, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Bilingual Education, 1979-1982 (Box 21)
    - Budget
      - General
        - 1979-1980 (Box 21)
        - 1980/1981 (Box 21)
        - 1981/1982 (Box 21)
        - 1983/1983 (Box 21)
      - Conference, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Faculty Merit Evaluation
        - 1980/1981 (Box 21)
        - 1981/1982 (Box 21)
      - Building Committee (renovation), 1977-1978 (Box 21)
    - Bureau of School Services
      - General
        - 1980 (Box 21)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 21)
      - Monthly Activity Summaries, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Bush Program in Child Development and Social Policy, 1980-1982 (Box 21)
    - Bylaw Changes, 1978-1979 (Box 21)
    - Career Education, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Carpenter Lecture, 1980-1983 (Box 21)
    - Centennial of the Establishment of the Chair of the Science and the Art of Teaching at the University of Michigan, 1978-1979 (Box 21)
    - Certification
      - 1980 (Box 21)
      - 1981 (Box 21)
      - 1982/1983 (Box 21)
    - Certification Manuals, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Child Care Action Center, 1970-1980 (Box 21)
    - Children's Center
      - 1978-1980 (Box 21)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 21)
    - Collegiate Institute for Values and Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box 21)
    - Combined Program in Education and Psychology
      - General
        - 1979-1980 (Box 21)
        - 1981-1985 (Box 21)
      - Executive Committee Minutes, 1979-1983 (Box 21)
      - Membership, 1960-1983 (Box 21)
      - Report (Box 22)
        - An Analysis of the Development and Present Status of the Combined Program in Education and Psychology, 1967 (Box 22)
        - Report of the Committee to Review, 1982 (Box 22)
        - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee, 1973 (Box 22)
    - Committees
      - Appraisal Committee
        - General
          - 1967 (Box 22)
          - 1968-1973 (Box 22)
          - 1977-1980 (Box 22)
        - Minutes, 1977-1981 (Box 22)
        - Report, 1969 (Box 22)
        - Review, 1977 (Box 22)
      - Committee on Committees, 1962-1969 (Box 22)
      - Curriculum Coordinating Committee
        - Minutes
          - 1977/78 (Box 22)
          - 1978/79 (Box 22)
          - 1979-1981 (Box 22)
        - Course Changes, 1980-1984 (Box 22)
        - General, 1979-1980 (Box 22)
      - Curriculum and Instruction Committee (minutes), 1978-1983 (Box 22)
      - Deanship, Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
      - Development, Curriculum, and Teaching (DCT) Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
      - Dissertation Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 22)
      - Elementary Education Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 22)
      - Executive Committee (retreat), 1985 (Box 22)
      - External Review Committee
        - General, 1976-1977 (Box 22)
        - Committee Visit, 1976/77 (Box 22)
        - Faculty Reactions (to Spurr report), 1977 (Box 22)
        - Spurr Report, 1977 (Box 22)
      - Graduate Committee
        - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 22)
        - General, 1981-1983 (Box 22)
      - Library Committee, 1979/80 (Box 22)
      - Ph.D. Review Committee, 1975-1983 (Box 22)
      - Professional Development Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
      - Promotions Committee
        - General
          - 1975/76 (Box 43)
          - 1976/77 (Box 43)
          - 1977/78 (Box 43)
          - 1978/79 (Box 43)
          - 1979/80 (Box 43)
          - 1980/81 (Box 43)
          - 1981/82 (Box 43)
          - 1982/83 (Box 43)
          - 1983/84 (Box 45)
          - 1984/85 (Box 45)
          - 1985/86 (Box 45)
            [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2016 ]
        - Procedures/Criteria, 1986-1986 (Box 23)
      - Reading Committee, 1970-1982 (Box 23)
      - Research, Measurement, and Evaluation Committee, 1987/88 (Box 23)
      - Search Committee (guidelines), 1978-1979 (Box 23)
      - Service and Institutional Relations Committee
        - Minutes, 1971-1982 (Box 23)
        - General, 1963-1982 (Box 23)
      - Undergraduate Committee
        - Minutes
          - 1958-1961 (Box 23)
          - 1961/62 (Box 23)
          - 1962/63 (Box 23)
          - 1963/64 (Box 23)
          - 1964/65 (Box 23)
          - 1965/66 (Box 23)
          - 1966/67 (Box 23)
          - 1967/68 (Box 23)
          - 1968/69 (Box 23)
          - 1969/70 (Box 23)
          - 1979-1983 (Box 23)
          - 1985/86, 2 folders (Box 23)
          - 1986/87 (Box 23)
          - 1987/88 (Box 23)
          - 1988/89 (Box 23)
        - General, 1980-1982 (Box 23)
        - Progress Report, 1985 (Box 23)
    - Committee Structure, 1978-1983 (Box 23)
    - Committee Memberships (faculty), 1978-1980 (Box 23)
    - Communication Disorders Clinics (review), 1981 (Box 23)
    - Community Service Resource Center, 1980 (Lippitt proposal) (Box 23)
    - Consortium for Evaluation Research, Training and Service (CERTS)
      - General, 1980-1982; 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Policy Council, 1980-1983 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Task Force, Report of, 1984 (Box 24)
    - Deans Council of Eight (Michigan), 1979-1980 (Box 24)
    - Dean's Network, 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Deans/Chairpersons Meeting Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 24)
    - Deans and Directors (DADS)
      - General, 1980-1985 (Box 24)
      - Proposed Guidelines for Student Teaching Programs, 1972 (Box 24)
    - Dearborn Campus
      - General, 1980-1982 (Box 24)
      - Division of Education, Executive Committee Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 24)
      - Joint Committee
        - General, 1978-1983 (Box 24)
        - Minutes, 1975-1981 (Box 24)
      - Task Force, 1979-1981 (Box 24)
    - Detroit Public Schools, 1971-1982 (Box 24)
    - Directed Teaching
      - General, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Assignments, 1981-1982 (Box 24)
      - Committee on Student Teaching, 1966-1969 (Box 24)
      - Music, 1957-1969 (Box 24)
      - Placement/Distribution, 1950-1970 (Box 24)
      - Remuneration, 1951-1972 (Box 24)
    - Dissertation
      - Abstracts, 1981/82 (Box 24)
      - Chairmanships (statistics), 1978-1982 (Box 24)
      - Review, 1978-1981 (Box 24)
    - Division and Committee Memberships, 1970-1982 (Box 25)
    - Divisional Assessment, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Doctoral Survey (from SOE Review, Exhibit #67)
      - Critique of Program, 1982 (Box 25)
      - Employment List of Graduates, 1964-1970 (Box 25)
      - Impact on Professional Life, 1982; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Impact of Masters Degree on Professional Life, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Early Childhood Development and Education, Center for
      - 1973-1978 (Box 25)
      - 1978-1982 (Box 25)
    - Education Alumni Society, 1971-1979 (Box 25)
    - Education and Community Development Program, 1978-1981 (Box 25)
    - Educational Administration and Supervision, Program in
      - General, 1979-1982; 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Masters Degree Sequence, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Educational Policy, Planning and Administration (EPPA),1982-1983 (Box 25)
    - Education Change Team, 1972 (Box 25)
    - Educational Psychology Program
      - General
        - 1960-1979 (Box 25)
        - (includes minutes), 1980-1982 (Box 25)
      - Paper Program Characteristics of Ph.D. Graduates in Educational Psychology from the University of Michigan; A Survey Analysis of 1969-1973 by Jackson & Dixon (Box 25)
      - Task Force, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Educational Resources Information Center/Counseling and Personnel Services (ERIC/CAPS), 1968-1983 (Box 25)
    - English and Education Program (Box 25)
      - General, 1980-1983; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Report of the Program Evaluation Committee, 1981 (Box 25)
    - English Composition Board, 1979-1982 (Box 25)
    - Enrollment, 1980-1983 (Box 25)
    - Evaluation and Planning Project
      - Phase I (background materials), 1975-1976 (Box 25)
      - Phase I (response), 1976 (Box 25)
      - Phase II, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
    - Executive Committee Memberships, 1969-1982 (Box 26)
    - Extension Service, 1980-1983; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Faculty Retreat
      - General, 1981 (Box 26)
      - Planning Council (includes minutes), 1981 (Box 26)
    - Faculty Workload, 1980-1982 (Box 26)